Contact

raflyfebriann@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/raflifebrian (LinkedIn) dribbble.com/zuckinggg (Portfolio) www.instagram.com/rfebriaann/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Codelgniter

Tailwind CSS

Web Design

Certifications

Computer Science Festival UIUX Technology Euphoria 2021 (Web Development)

KMIPN (Hackathon)

E-Wallet User Research Challenge JOINTSCAMP: Front-end Web Development

Rafli Febrian

Freelance Graphic Designer

Pekanbaru, Riau, Indonesia

Summary

Rafli is an enthusiastic learner and is currently pursuing visualrelated fields such as Graphic Design and UI Design. After going through a lot of development as a coder in college, he is now a UX researcher trying to understand user problems and their needs.

As a UX researcher, Rafli is responsible for studying and analyzing user behavior to inform user-friendly and easy-to-use product designs. He uses a variety of research methods, including usability testing, surveys, and interviews, to gather insights and feedback from users.

Currently, Rafli has completed his bachelor degree in Information Systems at the Caltex Riau Polytechnic with his final assignment in the field of UIUX by creating a mobile prototype called BrandQu which focuses on connecting influencers with Small and Medium Enterprise (SME) in doing branding using the design thinking method.

Experience

Freelance

Freelance Graphic Designer
January 2021 - Present (2 years 9 months)

One Street Food
Graphic Designer
October 2021 - August 2023 (1 year 11 months)

Jl. Pemuda No.59, Tampan, Kec. Payung Sekaki, Kota Pekanbaru, Riau 28291

Education

Politeknik Caltex Riau

D4, Sistem Informasi · (2019 - 2023)